

# **Petro Sych**

### **Contacts**

#### **Address**

Ukraine, Lviv

#### **Phone**

+380685889539

#### Email

sych.petro.a@gmail.com

### Skype

netter1993

### github

github.com/PetroSuch

Add to favorites

Download CV

# **Professional Summary**

3+ year experience as a Front-End dev. I am interested in Angular and I'm looking for a job that will help me improve my skills.

Responsible, diligent, reliable, able to listen, friendly, able to learn quickly and team player.

Also I like studying English and my goal to speak fluently in English.

## **Work Experience**

ARTBANK, Angular developer

05.2019 - now

I have been working in this company for 3 years. In the begining I started using AngularJs. My first project was a constructor forms based on a project "formio". Now i am using Angular 11 and Angular Native at my work. I am developing three mobile applications using Angular Native (iOS / Android) (a marketplace, a marketplace warehouse and an online wallet)

SPR.ru Front-end developer

10.2017 - 05.2019

During this period, I was working there a front-end AngularJs developer. I did HTML/CSS, AngualrJs part of project. Also i was developing a cabinet of customer.

alextyschenko.com Front-end developer

10.2017 - 05.2019

It is a web-studio where i was a front-end developer. My responsibilities included: HTML/CSS, Angular developping, SEO optimization web sites. I did a server side rendering for SEO optimizations. I did a part of API developing as well. We used Yii2 php framework for our API.

We were doing a project about an online CV constructor. I did a front-end part for whole project.

## **Additional Education**

Front-end web dev books

Typescript: The Complete Developer's Guide 05.2020

Angular - The Complete Guide (incl Angular Universal) 09.2020

## **Education**

**Ukrainian National Forestry University** 

2013 - 2019

now

## Languages

Ukrainian – native English – Intermediate Russian - native

# Technical skills

- Angular2+, AngularJs, Angular Universal, RxJs
- JS, ES6, TS, RestAPI
- HTML5
- CSS3, SCSS, SASS, LESS
- Git, Bitbucket
- Photoshop, Illustrator, Sketch, Postman

Add to favorites

Download CV